<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="releasenotes_title">Release Notes</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_value">
++ Version 1.18 ++\n
Added Renaissance\n
++ Version 1.17.2 ++\n
German Nocturne Translations by Martin Binder.\n
++ Version 1.17.1 ++\n
Updated Spanish Translations, too Nocturne Cards ALL, Crypt Card (Kingdom card).\n
Updated Spanish Translations Dismantle Promo.\n
By Diego and Diego.\n
++ Version 1.17 ++\n
Nocturne Cards added - English only at this stage.\n
Dismantle Promo added - English only at this stage.\n
Translation for all other cards to Spanish, by Diego and Diego. To date 11/11/2017.\n
++ Version 1.16.2 ++\n
Further fixes to incorrect German translations, by Martin Binder and bin101.\n
++ Version 1.16.1 ++\n
Fixes to missed and incorrect translations.\n
++ Version 1.16 ++\n
Finnish Translations added by Joonas Lahtiharju.\n
Polish Translations added by Pawel Pawlak.\n
(Release Notes not included for both translations).\n
Updated Dutch Translations by Tom Vandeweyer.\n
++ Version 1.15.4 ++\n
Updated German Translations by Martin Binder.\n
++ Version 1.15.3 ++\n
New Icon Graphics by EldVarg.\n
Added Events and Landmarks group to allow for rule of no more than 2.\n
Added code for Obelisk Card (Doesn\'t currently pick Ruins pile however).\n
++ Version 1.15.2 ++\n
Added 2nd Ed cards, and Sauna/Avanto Promo to appropriate Groups.\n
++ Version 1.15.1 ++\n
Sauna/Avanto Promo Added.\n
++ Version 1.15 ++\n
2nd Edition Base Dominion and Intrigue.\n
Cards in both sets will show as Base Set, Cards only in 1st Ed will show as Base Set 1st Ed., and Cards only in 2nd Ed will show as Base Set 2nd Ed. Similar for Intrigue cards.\n
Translations for German/Dutch are via Google Translate currently. I apologise to speakers of the languages for any botching of it.
++ Version 1.14 ++\n
Empires!\n
English only at this time.\n
++ Version 1.13 ++\n
New Dutch Translations added by Tom Vandeweyer.\n
++ Version 1.12 ++\n
New German Translations added by Christoph Moritz.\n
Added Summon Promo Card\n
Fixed Bug in Generating Bane for Young Witch\n
++ Version 1.11 ++\n
New Languages System. Only one copy of the core data to keep updated, and then translations for all the names, types, and descriptions, etc.\n
If anyone is willing to provide translations I\'ll add them in.\n
\n
++ Version 1.10 ++\n
Added ability to draw more or less than 10 cards.\n
Don\'t draw Potions, Ruins, Spoils, or Supplementary cards (e.g. Madman for Hermit) - These aren\'t needed in the App, as you should know to grab them when you pull out the other card.\n
Disabled Card Language Selector (since it\'s currently broken, apologies again to non-English speakers).\n
Moved both of the above options into a single Settings area.\n
Added Default Settings of: All Cards included. Maximum of 2 Events. Will only be set if the App is started with no pre-existing data.\n
Remove Shuffle from Menu - Should be accessed from the Shuffle Tab.\n
\n
++ Version 1.9 ++\n
Built upon Joran Jessurun\'s version\n
Added Adventures Cards\n
Added Events, and updated behaviour to not count Events against drawn Kingdom Cards.\n
\n
++ Known Bugs ++\n
Non-English Languages are not working (Sorry).
    </string>
</resources>